mpsoftware.dk 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy | MPSOFTWARE

  | 

Last update: September, 2009

**What information do we collect?  
**We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.   

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toï¿½keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?  
**We do not use cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Your Consent  
**By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

|   |
